Do you remember
how First Wife died?
Should I tell them?
First Wife...
Her soul was stolen by the Flower Demon.
First Wife!
First Wife has returned!
Oh, First Wife!
Chunmei,
First Wife...
What's her background?
First Wife's family
is the biggest tea merchant in Lijia Town.
First Wife loved flowers.
After marrying into the Li Manor,
she planted flowers all over the garden.
Besides planting flowers,
she also loved drinking tea.
Whenever the tea shop got new tea,
First Wife would personally brew it
for Master Li to try.
The couple had a harmonious relationship,
and lived a very peaceful life.
Until that day...
the Flower Demon came.
When the Flower Demon arrived,
a gust of wind blew.
The Flower Demon drained their essence,
making them wither instantly.
The Flower Demon also targeted First Wife.
On that very day,
First Wife, just like always,
was brewing tea for the master.
But the Flower Demon
didn't spare her.
Madam!
Somebody, help!
Somebody come quick!
First Wife is dead!
Why didn't you call the police?
Of course we called the police.
Master Li even asked Chief Mu to investigate.
But...
Chief Mu.
You're finally here.
First Wife was perfectly fine.
How did she suddenly die?
She had no external injuries.
And we found no poison in the manor.
We really can't determine the cause of death.
Do you think First Wife...
...had some hidden illness...
...and died from a sudden attack?
First Wife was in great health.
What hidden illness could she have?
It was the Flower Demon that killed her.
The so-called Flower Demon...
...is often found in ancient monster tales.
Flowers turning into spirits to harm mortals.
Don't talk nonsense.
We're investigating a case right now.
Not writing a storybook.
Chunmei.
Did First Wife...
...wear a white qipao?
Yes, how did...
How did you know?
We all saw it.
First Wife really became a ghost.
Look at how timid you are.
There's no such thing as ghosts or demons.
We must believe in science.
Stop spreading feudal superstitions.
She-devil!
Chunmei,
Keep preparing the wedding clothes.
We're going for a walk.
What do we do? They're going to investigate.
Master.
First Wife's grave is right there.
Are we really going to open the coffin?
What if it attracts the Flower Demon?
Flower Demon.
I'd like to see what she looks like.
What did you find?
First Wife's grave...
...why is it the exact same shape as the Li Manor?
Both are Haunted Houses.
A Haunted House?
How can you tell it's a Haunted House?
It's mentioned in The Classic of Lu Ban.
If built wide in front, narrow in back,
it will be restless all year round.
Energy leaks, turning it ominous.
The Li Manor is built exactly like that.
But I never expected...
First Wife's grave to be the same shape.
That's strange.
Why make both the manor and the grave
into Haunted Houses?
What nonsense.
Who cares if it's a manor or a grave?
Aren't they just built of wood and lime?
What's so haunted about them?
In my opinion,
the only things that harm people...
...are people.
First Wife.
Sorry for the intrusion.
Please forgive us.
First Wife didn't die of illness.
She died of poisoning.
Poisoning?
Yes.
There are no signs of poison on the body.
So my dad couldn't determine the cause.
Strange.
In First Wife's blood,
why is there a scent of plants?
You have a dog's nose.
It's that sensitive?
When I was a kid, I hated studying.
So my dad
would hide all the tasty food.
If I didn't study, he wouldn't let me eat.
But no matter where he hid it,
I could always find it.
Over time, with all that sniffing,
my sense of smell just got sharper.
So your nose
can only smell food.
Not exactly.
My dad forced me to study Bencao Gangmu.
He made me smell every herb in the world.
Back then, going into the mountains...
What's wrong?
I remember now.
I've smelled this scent before.
It was at the Li Manor.
When we passed by the garden.
Okay. Pack this up.
Let's go to the garden.
Okay.
I'm not going.
That garden must have a Flower Demon.
First Wife was killed by the Flower Demon.
Fine.
Then in a bit,
you can stay right here
and tell stories to First Wife.
She-devil!
Alright, I...
Stop messing around.
Solving the case is what matters.
Hurry up.
Quick.
Hold this.
Come on.
This is First Wife's garden.
Before First Wife died,
something strange happened in the garden.
The flowers she painstakingly grew
all died overnight.
Tell me,
do these flowers and First Wife's death
have anything to do with each other?
Oleander.
The scent on First Wife's remains
is exactly the same.
Oleander.
This flower is highly toxic.
Once poisoned,
it causes convulsions,
heart failure,
and even coughing up blood.
It seems
First Wife was poisoned by Oleander.
What is it?
There's a lot of Caustic Soda in the soil.
What withered the flowers in the garden
wasn't some Flower Demon.
It was the Caustic Soda in this soil.
Caustic Soda is highly corrosive.
So,
that's what caused the plants to die.
I'm a little confused.
Why would the killer
want to destroy all these plants?
To destroy evidence.
By destroying the garden's plants,
the police couldn't trace the poison.
But I still don't think it makes sense.
First Wife knew everything about flowers.
Why would she ingest Oleander poison?
First Wife loved drinking tea.
The tea is stored in the warehouse.
Let's go check the warehouse.
Maybe we'll find some clues.
Let's go.
Born into a family of tea merchants,
knowing tea inside out since childhood.
Pu'er is mellow,
Longjing is crisp.
What tea did you really drink that day?
March 7th, four months ago.
First Wife died right after drinking tea.
What tea?
On March 6th,
Dai's Tea Shop sent five packs of new tea.
It was called
Desert Rose Tea.
Desert Rose Tea. Desert Rose Tea.
It's my first time hearing of this tea.
This Desert Rose,
in both appearance and smell,
is very similar to Oleander.
It seems the killer
used the Oleander from the garden
to replace the Desert Rose.
So First Wife
drank the highly toxic Oleander
and was poisoned to death.
Does this killer really hate rich people?
Look,
Mengzhu was a wealthy lady,
and First Wife was also rich.
Chunmei said on the day First Wife died,
Master Li had mouth sores
and couldn't drink hot tea.
So he didn't drink
the Desert Rose Tea First Wife prepared.
My deduction was right.
The killer's target
was Master Li.
But they accidentally killed First Wife.
So Mengzhu was also killed by mistake?
Exactly.
My three wives,
Mengzhu,
I didn't take good care of you.
I'm truly sorry.
May your spirits in heaven
please protect me
and keep me safe.
Chief Mu.
That's not right.
Madam.
We're getting married tomorrow morning.
My father already told me.
But,
he asked me, before I marry you,
to look into the Li family murders first.
Sure.
The whole Li manor is your home now.
Investigate as you please.
Okay.
Then you must also know
that current evidence shows
you are the killer's target.
Then you'd better protect me well.
From now on,
you need to stay by my side at all times.
Then tell me the truth first.
Do you have any enemies at all?
You wrong me, Madam!
Who could I have a grudge against?
Everyone calls me Benefactor Li.
Do you know why?
In the past, Lijia Town
was dirt poor.
Ever since I came to Lijia Town,
I paid to build bridges and pave roads.
I opened a gold shop for business
and boosted the economy.
So,
everyone calls me Benefactor Li.
So everyone in town could live well,
I donated both money and goods.
Who could I have a grudge against?
It's the Flowing Cloud Pattern again.
Why does the Li family have so many
items from the Yuncang Kingdom?
You really don't have any enemies?
It's the absolute truth!
I even paid to build your police station.
Right now, half of Lijia Town
was built using my funds.
Who would I have a grudge against?
That's strange then.
We must find the motive first
to track down the killer.
The people of Lijia Town
have all benefited from you.
They have no reason to kill you.
Who's there?